ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4054
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files
1971-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
McKersie, Robert B.
Doherty, Robert E.
/4054
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3085053
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
M. Clark, January 26, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4033: Robert McKersie Files /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional 5464: U.S. Economic Stabilization Program Records
McKersie, Robert B.; Doherty, Robert E.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office.
3085053
- FMCS Program, Washington, Sept. 21, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Convocation - February 12, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- OFCC/AF Action Conf. - Oct. 31-Nov. 2, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- McKersie -- Various Progs. Attended/participate in (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Bronfenbrenner - Fam. Stresses & Support Project (Box 8, Folder 5)
- CED Subcomm. On Improving Prod. In Govt. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- IRRA Executive Board -- 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Washington - President's Commission on Coal -- 3/21/79, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Penny Schantz -- Grad School Appl. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Cornell Club (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Master Charge (Box 8, Folder 11)
- McKersie - Rough Drafts (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Brown & Williamson Tobacco Co. - consulting (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Publication Requests (Box 8, Folder 14)
- McKersie Personal - Miscellaneous Booklets and Publications (Box 8, Folder 15)
- IRRA Productivity Volume - 1975 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Letters re Deanship (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Evening Seminars Dean's Home (Box 8, Folder 18)
- ILR 651 -- Spring 1979 -- Dean's Course (Box 8, Folder 19)
- McKersie, Travel Expenses 1976-79, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 1)
- McKersie, Robert B. Travel, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Administrative Board -- Cornell Univ. Council (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Continuity of Employment Committee (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Jan. 1979- (Box 9, Folder 5)
- June, 1978-Dec. 1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- 1976 to Dec. 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Jan. 1978-May, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Apr. 1977-Mar. 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Reports (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Resumes (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Mental Hygiene Assessment Program (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Contracts (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Contracts (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Minutes of Meetings (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Expenses (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Overview of ILR school, includes back up material. (Box 11)
  - Testing Academic Freedom (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Testing Academic Freedom (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - AAA - Case No. 15 30 0160 78 -- Jt. Bd., TWUA vs. Boise Cascade, Inc. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PERB Case No. A78-164 -- Roch. City Dist. Vs. Roch. Teachers Assoc. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Case - A77-42 -- (Town of Clifton, Highway D. Truck Drivers, Local 687) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - AAA -- Case No. 15 39 0266 76 (Fabius-Pompey Ed. Assoc) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Vince Macri Story (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - AAA -- RE: 15 39 0109 77 -- (CSEA and Indian River Cent. School, Watertown) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - IRRA (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - PERB -- CA-0070; M75-682 (Village of Alden and Alden P.B.A.) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Staff Affairs (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - AAA -- #15 39 0051 77 N. Warren Teachers Asso. Vs. N. Warren Central School (Box 11, Folder 15)
- General Dean's files, 1971-1979. (Box 12)
  - Nancy's Notes (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Candidates drafts (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Olivia Mitchell Story (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Search mat'l. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Notes (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Notes (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Prudential (AOL) Bob (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - File in Box (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - ILR Pubs. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Doctor's Appts. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - ILR at 50 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sermon, "A Pilgrim at the Bargaining Table," Sage Chapel -- December 5, 1976 - Robert B. McKersie (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Labor Studies (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Employment Security (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Labor College (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - A Design and Methodology for Conducting Evaluation of a Quality of Work Program: Abstract -- Draft and notes (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Ford (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Minority Employment (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Planning CC Episode (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Curriculum Mat'l.; Student Petitions; Admissions (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Tickets to Nepal (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Personnel - Faculty Mat'l. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Harry Van Arsdale Jr. Memorial Assoc. (Box 12, Folder 23)